Start it.
I'm sorry.
You have the camera.
Yeah, it started record.
Okay,
so I don't think it should like bug
So for like first thing.
should be found by unlisting the logs.
Okay.
Okay,
but should be actually found actually
after many exports they have.
Yeah.
Part of the reason is, actually,
let's say like a actually is a record
section first and then it first actually
it will already like essentially like for
every next step,
it has to analyse the current current
screen shot.
And it might have to actually look at the
like a action earlier action.
Because at any given point in time.
Just lets say like the current state as
well as the last action might not be
enough for the CLM to understand like
what is currently happening. Okay,
it is a sequence of actions. I did this,
I did this, I did this, I did this.
Now I am here what to do mention so just.
Actually,
the last nap that is not be good enough.
Hello.
Actually,
essentially what should happen is it
should have a tool to analyse the log.
Airmen should have a tool to analyse the
actions.
Okay,
but actually identifying the bugs should
happen live.
Whenever actually it is working,
you get current screenshot.
Hello.
So,
if it is not actually like working as per
expectation,
it should be able to record a finding.
Right.
The finding itself separate table all
together.
Hello.
Maybe the finding table itself might be
used to communicate with you.
Okay,
or else like lets say like it can
actually add a lets say like a value to
print that and then present it to you.
Yeah.
OK,
like either there will be 3 tables or 4
tables, OK,
but just actually unleasing the like logs
alone will not actually give it the
necessary content.
It will be only partial.
Haan.
So like just actually like make sure like
it is documented and the action is shown
in the diagram before going for
implementation.
Yeah.
Because actually,
if actually they endorsement and the
diagram is not right,
it actually initially even seem like it
is working.
But after something, it will not work.
So get the diagram break.
Yeah.
Get that I am right. Actually,
for you should be like basically you
should be like essentially with that.
It should be able to convince you the
diagram,
even if you have actually some doubts
without the diagram like just actually
get it clarified with it and if need is
like if you think actually the something
Yeah.
should be detailed,
ask it to create a new diagram along with
Yeah.
the old diagram to add detail.
In that every diagram has a have a
description beneath it.
Hello.
Like just actually go through like say
like the document actually and then
implement it and then the implementation
can happen in card.
Hello.
Just action like record the action,
switch up the screenshots on WhatsApp,
Hello.
let there be activation one step.
And then actually bring in the actually
the findings.
Yeah, got.
And actually the way to make sure I
actually get working is to like a give it
some buggy level.
Basically,
there is one other thing we are not
talking about actually an app that works
with existing content,
we are talking about live exploration.
Haan.
No.
So like you could actually basically you
could actually ask the AE 2 and there is
one other thing,
it should not have access to the code.
Hello.
So just actually it can launch the binary
basically it can launch the application,
but it should not have access to the code.
That should be that should be there.
All is actually it will stop actually
looking at the application if it start
No.
looking at the code for.
Yeah.
Okay,
do like you can add I want to isolate
like there are actually there are 2 A's
like one A that you will you are using
for developing this application and
actually one one other thing it is
actually test the application.
They should be separate and actually
development day you felt that actually
the testing a should not have access to
the code base. How do I suggest that?
So that is just actually looked at like
and the second thing is give me one
Han.
minute.
No problem.
So the second thing is actually to make
sure the water application it says as a
bug that you already know.
Yeah.
Expected to find it.
Basically, like a 2 level,
the extended internet actually will do
something okay,
and it should be like definitely like a
university level.
What?
Anytime you create your own game,
basically when you develop this,
it does not have to test the GD match.
Yeah.
Create a simple joke.
Okay.
And after 230.
Got it.
Our term testing will be better,
not sneakers.
Live action games like Shielded,
you will not be able to manage the speed.
Essentially, to actually to play snake,
it should be able to look at the scene
every every second is not less than that.
So create like a of a board game or a
Okay, got it.
puzzle and then ask to solve it.
Got it.
And don't have complicated person,
complicated person just actually 4 times,
Hello.
5 times or something like that.
And have a level with like explicit bug.
Hello.
Hey,
actually it should not be able to like
basically renew chat actually it should
not work or actually like there should be
Mhm.
unsolvable level or something like that.
Try to actually make it find it fixing
its not its responsibility.
Oh.
Okay,
and actually just actually have some
anomaly too and actually so that you can
give it some excuse. Basically,
don't care about this item,
it should be able to like take that into
account.
It's all like a see like a see some
sensor. Sector.
Get the Atkinson skin short blog.
OK, second, what is it I forgot? Firstly,
give the action and slim shot slot,
second actually make it identify the bug,
3rd will give you the exceptions and
actually they make it actually sound
exceptions when it actually both of them.
Just actually we have planned for one
step at a time, not all the steps.
No.
Yeah.
Initially,
don't worry about backup description.
It's all my issue.
yeah.
Even if the data is lost,
it's not a problem.
Got you.
Backup actually, it is part of hardening,
not part of initial exploration.
Anything else?
No, as of now.
Oh.
Bye.